Guide to the Harlequin Romance Collection of Treva M. Taylor 1967-1996 (Bulk 1974-1996) MSS.216
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Harlequin Romance Novels
  - Harlequin Romance 1521. Perkins, Barbara: My Sisters and Me. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1522. Hampson, Anne: Love Hath an Island. (Harlequin Books), 1971 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Harlequin Romance 1523. Ferrari, Ivy: House of Clouds. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1524. Seale, Sara: Dear Professor. (Harlequin Books), 1971 (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Harlequin Romance 1525. Britt, Katrina: The Unknown Quest. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1526. Barrie, Susan: Bride in Waiting. (Harlequin Books), 1971 (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - Harlequin Romance 1527. Doyle, Amanda: Dilemma at Dulloora. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1528. Reid, Henrietta: The Made Marriage. (Harlequin Books), 1971 (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Harlequin Romance 1529. Neels, Betty: Tulips for Augusta. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1530. Way, Margaret: The Man from Bahl Bahla. (Harlequin Books), 1971 (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Harlequin Romance 1531. Westwood, Gwen: Castle of the Unicorn. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1532. Andersen, Jan: The Man in the Shadow. (Harlequin Books), 1971 (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Harlequin Romance 1533. Gillen, Lucy: The Girl at Smuggler's Rest. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1534. Ashton, Elizabeth: Cousin Mark. (Harlequin Books), 1971 (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - Harlequin Romance 1535. Summers, Essie: The House on Gregor's Brae. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1536. Hilton, Margery: Trust in Tomorrow (original title: Miss Columbine and Harley Quinn). (Harlequin Books), 1971 (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - Harlequin Romance 1537. Dunbar, Jean: The Summer Nights. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1538. Hoy, Elizabeth: It Happened in Paris. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - Harlequin Romance 1539. Malcolm, Margaret: Next Door to Romance. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1540. Kidd, Flora: The Dazzle on the Sea. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - Harlequin Romance 1541. Dingwell, Joyce: Clove Orange. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1542. Pollock, Rosemary: The Mountains of Spring. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - Harlequin Romance 1543. Burchell, Mary: But Not For Me. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1544. Arbor, Jane: The Other Miss Donne. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - Harlequin Romance 1545. Norrell, Marjorie: Pride's Banner. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1546. Wilde, Hilary: The Master of Barracuda Isle. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - Harlequin Romance 1547. Lane, Roumelia: Café Mimosa. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1548. Donnelly, Jane: Halfway to the Stars. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 5, Folder 104)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233299
  - Harlequin Romance 1549. Cork, Dorothy: A Night for Possums. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1550. Whistler, Mary: Pathway of Roses. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 5, Folder 105)
  - Harlequin Romance 1551. Hampson, Anne: Stars of Spring. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1552. MacLeod, Jean S.: The Way Through the Valley. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 5, Folder 106)
  - Harlequin Romance 1553. Gillen, Lucy: Doctor Toby. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1554. Rowan, Barbara: The Keys of the Castle. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 5, Folder 107)
  - Harlequin Romance 1555. Winspear, Violet: Raintree Valley. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1556. Nickson, Hilda: No Enemy. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 5, Folder 108)
  - Harlequin Romance 1557. Moore, Mary: Along the Ribbonwood Track. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1558. Danbury, Iris: Legend of Roscano. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 5, Folder 109)
  - Harlequin Romance 1559. Nel, Stella Frances: A Singing Bird. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1560. Ferrari, Ivy: Windy Night, Rainy Morrow. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 5, Folder 110)
  - Harlequin Romance 1561. Chace, Isobel: Home is Goodbye. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1562. Doyle, Amanda: Kookaburra Dawn. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 5, Folder 111)
  - Harlequin Romance 1563. Malcolm, Margaret: This Tangled Web. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1564. Summers, Essie: South Island Stowaway. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 5, Folder 112)
  - Harlequin Romance 1565. Pressley, Hilda: Harbinger of Spring. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1566. Dingwell, Joyce: September Street. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 5, Folder 113)
  - Harlequin Romance 1567. Burchell, Mary: Do Not Go, My Love. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1568. Cummins, Mary: Sea Tangle. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 5, Folder 114)
  - Harlequin Romance 1569. Neels, Betty: Tangled Autumn. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1570. Hampson, Anne: Heaven is High. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 5, Folder 115)
  - Harlequin Romance 1571. Way, Margaret: Summer Magic. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1572. Peake, Lilian: This Moment in Time. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 5, Folder 116)
  - Harlequin Romance 1573. Kidd, Flora: Love is Fire. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1574. Mather, Anne: Lord of Zaracus. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 5, Folder 117)
  - Harlequin Romance 1575. Reid, Henrietta: Sister of the Bride. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1576. Bevan, Gloria: It Began in Te Rangi. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 5, Folder 118)
  - Harlequin Romance 1577. Norrell, Marjorie: Dr. Maitland's Secretary (original title: The Doctor's Secretary). (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1578. Moore, Mary: Rata Flowers are Red. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 5, Folder 119)
  - Harlequin Romance 1579. Gillen, Lucy: Winter at Cray. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1580. Winspear, Violet. Black Douglas. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 5, Folder 120)
  - Harlequin Romance 1581. Hilton, Marjorie: The House of the Amulet. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1582. Arbor, Jane: Wildfire Quest. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 5, Folder 121)
  - Harlequin Romance 1583. Thorpe, Kay: Sawdust Season. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1584. Farnes, Eleanor: A Castle in Spain. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 5, Folder 122)
  - Harlequin Romance 1585. Armstrong, Juliet: The Flowering Valley. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1586. Chace, Isobel: To Marry a Tiger. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 5, Folder 123)
  - Harlequin Romance 1587. Burchell, Mary: Music of the Heart. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1588. Cust, Barbara: The Leaping Flame. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 5, Folder 124)
  - Harlequin Romance 1589. Dingwell, Joyce: Nickel Wife. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1590. Nelson, Valerie K.: The Girl from Over the Sea. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 5, Folder 125)
  - Harlequin Romance 1591. Wilde, Hilary: Operation - In Search of Love. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1592. Donnelly, Jane: The Mill in the Meadow. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 6, Folder 126)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233307
  - Harlequin Romance 1593. Neels, Betty: Wish with the Candles. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1594. Peake, Lilian: Mist Across the Moors. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 6, Folder 127)
  - Harlequin Romance 1595. Hampson, Anne: Gold is the Sunrise. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1596. Quentin, Dorothy: The Inn by the Lake. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 6, Folder 128)
  - Harlequin Romance 1597. Seale, Sara: The Unknown Mr. Brown (original title: Mr. Brown). (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1598. Slide, Dorothy: Star in a Dark Sky. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 6, Folder 129)
  - Harlequin Romance 1599. Smith, Doris E.: Dear Deceiver. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1600. Mather, Anne: The Reluctant Governess. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 6, Folder 130)
  - Harlequin Romance 1601. Pressley, Hilda: The Newcomer. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1602. Kidd, Flora: Remedy for Love. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 6, Folder 131)
  - Harlequin Romance 1603. Way, Margaret: Ring of Jade. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1604. Gillen, Lucy: That Man Next Door. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 6, Folder 132)
  - Harlequin Romance 1605. Hoy, Elizabeth: Immortal Flower. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1606. Dunbar, Jean: The Quiet Veld. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 6, Folder 133)
  - Harlequin Romance 1607. Malcolm, Margaret: Not Less Than All. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1608. Bevan, Gloria: Vineyard in a Valley. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 6, Folder 134)
  - Harlequin Romance 1609. Thorpe, Kay: Not Wanted on Voyage. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1610. Hilton, Margery: Dear Conquistador. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 6, Folder 135)
  - Harlequin Romance 1611. Rome, Margaret: Chateau of Flowers. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1612. Cummins, Mary: Mistress of Elvan Hall. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 6, Folder 136)
  - Harlequin Romance 1613. MacLeod, Jean S.: Moment of Decision. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1614. Lindsay, Rachel: Love and Lucy Granger. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 6, Folder 137)
  - Harlequin Romance 1615. Dingwell, Joyce: A Thousand Candles. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1616. Winspear, Violet: The Pagan Island. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 6, Folder 138)
  - Harlequin Romance 1617. Shore, Juliet: Tree of Promise. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1618. Chace, Isobel: The Wealth of the Islands. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 6, Folder 139)
  - Harlequin Romance 1619. Clemence, Ruth: Happy with Either. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1620. Danbury, Iris: Jacaranda Island. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 6, Folder 140)
  - Harlequin Romance 1621. Reid, Henrietta: Garth of Tregillis. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1622. Hampson, Anne: There Came a Tyrant. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 6, Folder 141)
  - Harlequin Romance 1623. Dell, Belinda: Flowers for the Festival. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1624. Wilde, Hilary: The Golden Maze. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 6, Folder 142)
  - Harlequin Romance 1625. Neels, Betty: Victory for Victoria. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1626. Britt, Katrina: A Spray of Edelweiss. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 6, Folder 143)
  - Harlequin Romance 1627. Gillen, Lucy: My Beautiful Heaven. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1628. Peake, Lilian: The Library Tree. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 6, Folder 144)
  - Harlequin Romance 1629. Weale, Anne: A Treasure for Life. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1630. Doyle, Amanda: Escape to Koolonga. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 6, Folder 145)
  - Harlequin Romance 1631. Mather, Anne: Masquerade. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1632. Burchell, Mary: One Man's Heart. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 6, Folder 146)
  - Harlequin Romance 1633. Dingwell, Joyce: Red Ginger Blossom. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1634. Hilton, Margery: The Spell of the Enchanter. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 6, Folder 147)
  - Harlequin Romance 1635. Malcolm, Margaret: Marriage by Agreement. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1636. Ashton, Elizabeth: Flutter of White Wings. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 7, Folder 148)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233315
  - Harlequin Romance 1637. Winspear, Violet: The Silver Slave. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1638. Westwood, Gwen: Pirate of the Sun. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 7, Folder 149)
  - Harlequin Romance 1639. Farnes, Eleanor: The Valley of the Eagles. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1640. Kidd, Flora: If Love Be Love. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 7, Folder 150)
  - Harlequin Romance 1641. Neels, Betty: The Fifth Day of Christmas. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1642. Wilde, Hilary: The Fire of Life. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 7, Folder 151)
  - Harlequin Romance 1643. McConnell, Margaret S.: The Glory or the Love. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1644. Cork, Dorothy: Wayaway. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 7, Folder 152)
  - Harlequin Romance 1645. Rome, Margaret: Bride of the Rif. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1646. Hampson, Anne: Isle of the Rainbows. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 7, Folder 153)
  - Harlequin Romance 1647. Nickson, Hilda: The Sweet Spring. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1648. Lindsay, Rachel: Moonlight and Magic. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 7, Folder 154)
  - Harlequin Romance 1649. Gillen, Lucy: Sweet Kate. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1650. Peake, Lilian: The Real Thing. (Harlequin Books), 1972 (Box 7, Folder 155)
  - Harlequin Romance 1651. Christian, Jill: A Scent of Lemons. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1652. Cummins, Mary: A Pearl for Love. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 7, Folder 156)
  - Harlequin Romance 1653. Chace, Isobel: The Tartan Touch. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1654. Lane, Roumelia: In the Shade of the Palms. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 7, Folder 157)
  - Harlequin Romance 1655. Burchell, Mary: It's Rumoured in the Village. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1656. Mather, Anne: Autumn of the Witch. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 7, Folder 158)
  - Harlequin Romance 1657. Dingwell, Joyce: Wife to Sim. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1658. Winspear, Violet: Dear Puritan. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 7, Folder 159)
  - Harlequin Romance 1659. Ashton, Elizaebth: A Parade of Peacocks. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1660. Donnelly, Jane: A Stranger Came. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 7, Folder 160)
  - Harlequin Romance 1661. Thorpe, Kay: Olive Island. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1662. Farnes, Eleanor: A Serpent in Eden. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 7, Folder 161)
  - Harlequin Romance 1663. Kidd, Flora: The Cave of the White Rose. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1664. Malcolm, Margaret: The Faithful Rebel. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 7, Folder 162)
  - Harlequin Romance 1665. Arbor, Jane: The Flower on the Rock. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1666. Neels, Betty: Saturday's Child. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 7, Folder 163)
  - Harlequin Romance 1667. Lindsay, Rachel: A Question of Marriage. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1668. Cork, Dorothy: Summer Mountain. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 7, Folder 164)
  - Harlequin Romance 1669. Gillen, Lucy: A Time Remembered. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1670. Hilton, Margery: Frail Sanctuary. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 7, Folder 165)
  - Harlequin Romance 1671. Danbury, Iris: Mandolins of Montori. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1672. Hampson, Anne: The Rebel Bride. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 7, Folder 166)
  - Harlequin Romance 1673. Chace, Isobel: A Pride of Lions. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1674. Peake, Lilian: Man Out of Reach. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 7, Folder 167)
  - Harlequin Romance 1675. Pollock, Rosemary: Song Above the Clouds. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1676. Rome, Margaret: The Girl at Eagle's Mount. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 7, Folder 168)
  - Harlequin Romance 1677. Coates, May: Stranger at the Door. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1678. Hampson, Anne: The Plantation Boss. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 7, Folder 169)
  - Harlequin Romance 1679. Britt, Katrina: The Gentle Flame. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1680. Winspear, Violet: Rapture of the Desert. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 7, Folder 170)
  - Harlequin Romance 1681. Donnelly, Jane: The Long Shadow. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1682. Bevan, Gloria: The Frost and the Fire. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 7, Folder 171)
  - Harlequin Romance 1683. Gillen, Lucy: Dangerous Stranger. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1684. Kidd, Flora: The Taming of Lisa. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 8, Folder 172)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233323
  - Harlequin Romance 1685. Wilde, Hilary: The Impossible Dream. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1686. Charlton, Madeline: Alpenrose. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 8, Folder 173)
  - Harlequin Romance 1687. Way, Margaret: Noonfire. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1688. Dingwell, Joyce: The Pool of the Pink Lilies. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 8, Folder 174)
  - Harlequin Romance 1689. Neels, Betty: Cassandra by Chance. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1690. Smith, Doris E.: The One and Only. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 8, Folder 175)
  - Harlequin Romance 1691. May, Wynne: A Bowl of Stars. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1692. Cork, Dorothy: Butterfly Montane. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 8, Folder 176)
  - Harlequin Romance 1693. MacLeod, Jean S.: Adam's Daughter (original title: Adam's Wife). (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1694. Armstrong, Juliet: The Tideless Sea. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 8, Folder 177)
  - Harlequin Romance 1695. Hoy, Elizabeth: That Island Summer. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1696. Leigh, Roberta: My Heart's a Dancer. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 8, Folder 178)
  - Harlequin Romance 1697. Clemence, Ruth: Healing in the Hills. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1698. Chace, Isobel: Cadence of Portugal. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 8, Folder 179)
  - Harlequin Romance 1699. Malcolm, Margaret: Sunshine on the Mountains. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1700. Peake, Lilian: Gone Before Morning. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 8, Folder 180)
  - Harlequin Romance 1701. Rome, Margaret: Bird of Paradis. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1702. Summers, Essie: A Touch of Magic. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 8, Folder 181)
  - Harlequin Romance 1703. Britt, Katrina: Reluctant Voyager. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1704. Burchell, Mary: Except My Love. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 8, Folder 182)
  - Harlequin Romance 1705. Neels, Betty: Three for a Wedding. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1706. Douglas, Monica: Shadow of the Past. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 8, Folder 183)
  - Harlequin Romance 1707. Gray, Janice: Garden of the Sun. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1708. Nel, Stella Frances: Golden Harvest. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 8, Folder 184)
  - Harlequin Romance 1709. Andersen, Jan: The Man from Coral Bay. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1710. Hilton, Margery: The Inshine Girl. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 8, Folder 185)
  - Harlequin Romance 1711. Gillen, Lucy: Summer Season. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1712. Moore, Mary: Matai Valley Magic. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 8, Folder 186)
  - Harlequin Romance 1713. Ashton, Elizabeth: Alpine Rhapsody. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1714. Cork, Dorothy: Spirit of the Sun. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 8, Folder 187)
  - Harlequin Romance 1715. Leigh, Roberta: In Name Only. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1716. Westwood, Gwen: Citadel of Swallows. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 8, Folder 188)
  - Harlequin Romance 1717. Wibberley, Mary: Black Niall. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1718. Nickson, Hilda: Lord of the Forest. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 8, Folder 189)
  - Harlequin Romance 1719. MacLeod, Jean S.: The Rainbow Days. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1720. Reid, Henrietta: Intruder at Windgates. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 8, Folder 190)
  - Harlequin Romance 1721. Chace, Isobel: The Falmboyant Tree. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1722. Lamb, Charlotte: Follow a Stranger. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 8, Folder 191)
  - Harlequin Romance 1723. Donnelly, Jane: Rocks Under Shining Water. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1724. Quentin, Dorothy: Wedding at Blue River. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 8, Folder 192)
  - Harlequin Romance 1725. Lewty, Marjorie: The Extraordinary Engagement. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1726. Peake, Lilian: Man in Charge. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 9, Folder 193)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233331
  - Harlequin Romance 1727. Britt, Katrina: Strange Bewilderment. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1728. Malcolm, Margaret: The Lonely Road. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 9, Folder 194)
  - Harlequin Romance 1729. Douglas, Sheila: The Young Doctor. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1730. Bevan, Gloria: Flame in Fiji. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 9, Folder 195)
  - Harlequin Romance 1731. Summers, Essie: The Forbidden Valley. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1732. Kidd, Flora: Beyond the Sunset. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 9, Folder 196)
  - Harlequin Romance 1733. Burchell, Mary: Call and I'll Come. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1734. Asquith, Nan: The Girl from Rome. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 9, Folder 197)
  - Harlequin Romance 1735. Wilde, Hilary: Temptations of the Moon. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1736. Gillen, Lucy: The Enchanted Ring. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 9, Folder 198)
  - Harlequin Romance 1737. Neels, Betty: Winter of Change. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1738. Dingwell, Joyce: The Mutual Look. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 9, Folder 199)
  - Harlequin Romance 1739. Wibberley, Mary: Beloved Enemy. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1740. Arbor, Jane: Roman Summer. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 9, Folder 200)
  - Harlequin Romance 1741. Ashton, Elizabeth: Moorland Magic. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1742. Lindsay, Rachel: Alien Corn. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 9, Folder 201)
  - Harlequin Romance 1743. Nel, Stella Frances: Destiny is a Flower. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1744. Gray, Janice: Winter Loving. (Harlequin Books), 1973 (Box 9, Folder 202)
  - Harlequin Romance 1745. Lane, Roumelia: Nurse at Noongwalla. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1746. Malcolm, Margaret: Without Any Amazement. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 9, Folder 203)
  - Harlequin Romance 1747. Weale, Anne: The Fields of Heaven. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1748. Stratton, Rebecca: The Golden Madonna. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 9, Folder 204)
  - Harlequin Romance 1749. Dell, Belinda: Lovely is the Rose. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1750. Chace, Isobel: The House of the Scissors, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 205)
  - Harlequin Romance 1751. Lamb, Charlotte: Carnival Coast. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1752. Hilton, Margery: Miranda's Marriage. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 9, Folder 206)
  - Harlequin Romance 1753. Asquith, Nan: Time May Change. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1754. Gillen, Lucy: The Pretty Witch. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 9, Folder 207)
  - Harlequin Romance 1755. Walsh, Penelope: School My Heart. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1756. Thorpe, Kay: An Apple in Eden. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 9, Folder 208)
  - Harlequin Romance 1757. Cork, Dorothy: The Girl at Saltbush Flat. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1758. Hunter, Elizabeth: The Crescent Moon. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 9, Folder 209)
  - Harlequin Romance 1759. Lewty, Marjorie: The Rest is Magic. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1760. Britt, Katrina: The Guarded Gates. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 9, Folder 210)
  - Harlequin Romance 1761. Neels, Betty: Stars Through the Mist. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1762. Ashton, Elizabeth: Sigh No More. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 9, Folder 211)
  - Harlequin Romance 1763. Lindsay, Rachel: Cage of Gold (two editions). (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 9, Folder 212)
  - Harlequin Romance 1764. Reid, Henrietta: Bird of Prey. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1765. Farnes, Eleanor: The Splendid Legacy. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 9, Folder 213)
  - Harlequin Romance 1766. Way, Margaret: Storm Over Mandargi. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1767. Burchell, Mary: Unbidden Melody. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 9, Folder 214)
  - Harlequin Romance 1768. Wilde, Hilary: The Palace of Gold. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1769. Hoy, Elizabeth: The Girl in the Green Valley. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 9, Folder 215)
  - Harlequin Romance 1769. Hoy, Elizabeth: The Girl in the Green Valley. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 1770. Stratton, Rebecca: Fairwinds. (Harlequin Books), 1974 (Box 10, Folder 216)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233349